[
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-169",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/majority-element/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/sorting/leetcode/P001_Majority_element.java",
    "name": "Majority element",
    "serialNum": 1,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-07",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Counting", "Divide and Conquer", "Hash Table", "Sorting"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": "Time limit exceeded",
    "id": "leetcode-217",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/contains-duplicate/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/sorting/leetcode/P002_Contains_duplicate.java",
    "name": "Contains duplicate",
    "serialNum": 2,
    "solutionAccepted": false,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-07",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Hash Table", "Sorting"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1637",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/widest-vertical-area-between-two-points-containing-no-points/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/sorting/leetcode/P003_Widest_vertical_area_between_two_points_containing_no_points.java",
    "name": "Widest vertical area between two points containing no points",
    "serialNum": 3,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-08",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Sorting"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2089",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-target-indices-after-sorting-array/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/sorting/leetcode/P004_Find_target_indices_after_sorting_array.java",
    "name": "Find target indices after sorting array",
    "serialNum": 4,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-08",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search", "Sorting"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-88",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/merge-sorted-array/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/sorting/leetcode/P005_Merge_sorted_array.java",
    "name": "Merge sorted array",
    "serialNum": 5,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-09",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Sorting", "Two Pointers"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-242",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-anagram/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/sorting/leetcode/P006_Valid_anagram.java",
    "name": "Valid anagram",
    "serialNum": 6,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-09",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Hash Table", "Sorting", "String"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2545",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/sort-the-students-by-their-kth-score/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/sorting/leetcode/P007_Sort_the_students_by_their_Kth_score.java",
    "name": "Sort the students by their Kth score",
    "serialNum": 7,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-10",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Matrix", "Sorting"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1561",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-number-of-coins-you-can-get/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/sorting/leetcode/P008_Maximum_number_of_coins_you_can_get.java",
    "name": "Maximum number of coins you can get",
    "serialNum": 8,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-10",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Game Theory", "Greedy", "Math","Sorting"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1630",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/arithmetic-subarrays/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/sorting/leetcode/P009_Arithmetic_subarrays.java",
    "name": "Arithmetic subarrays",
    "serialNum": 9,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-11",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Hash Table","Sorting"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-268",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/missing-number/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/sorting/leetcode/P010_Missing_number.java",
    "name": "Missing number",
    "serialNum": 10,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-11",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search", "Bit Manipulation", "Hash Table", "Math", "Sorting"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2160",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-sum-of-four-digit-number-after-splitting-digits/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/sorting/leetcode/P011_Minimum_sum_of_four_digit_number_after_splitting_digits.java",
    "name": "Minimum sum of four digit number after splitting digits",
    "serialNum": 11,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-06",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Greedy", "Math", "Sorting"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-2974",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-sum-of-four-digit-number-after-splitting-digits/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/sorting/leetcode/P012_Minimum_number_game.java",
    "name": "Minimum number game",
    "serialNum": 12,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-07",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Heap (Priority Queue)", "Simulation", "Sorting"]
  },
  {
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "error": null,
    "id": "leetcode-1337",
    "linkProblem": "https://leetcode.com/problems/the-k-weakest-rows-in-a-matrix/description/",
    "linkSolution" : "https://github.com/suman-saurabh-das/problem-solving__dsa__java/blob/main/src/sorting/leetcode/P013_The_K_weakest_rows_in_a_matrix.java",
    "name": "The K weakest rows in a matrix",
    "serialNum": 13,
    "solutionAccepted": true,
    "solvedOn" : "2024-05-08",
    "source": "leetcode",
    "topics" : ["Array", "Binary Search", "Heap (Priority Queue)", "Matrix", "Sorting"]
  }
]